<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tab Experiment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tab_1">These are the top stories:</string>
    <string name="tab_2">Technology news you can read:</string>
    <string name="tab_3">Cooking tips:</string>

    <string name="tab_label1">Top Stories</string>
    <string name="tab_label2">Technology News</string>
    <string name="tab_label3">Cooking</string>

    <string name="tab_11"> \u0020 \u0020 I love the idea of long-range hiking routes.
        Typically arranged to support multi-day itineraries, these kinds
        of routes let you go out and lose yourself on the trail (Note: not the same as getting lost).
        My latest look into the world of long-range hiking routes had me checking out Spain’s “GR”
        or Gran Recorrido routes. There are 13 GR routes in Spain and two of them, GR221 and GR222
        are located on the island of Mallorca.
        \n\n \u0020 \u0020 The GR221 is also called ‘Ruta de pedra en sec’ (Dry Stone Route) and it strings its
        way through the dramatic Serra de Tramuntana mountain range that pretty well covers the Northern coast of
        the island. The Tramuntanas are a UNESCO World Heritage Site for their significance as a
        cultural landscape. Dry stone masonry, much of it centuries old, is everywhere along the
        route: terrace walls on steep slopes, houses and barns, walls separating fields, and even
        much of the surface of the pathway are built using a distinctive style of dry stone masonry
        that form-fits the stones without mortar or cement between them. The entire GR221 route is
        about 173 kilometers but chunks of it are still under development.
        A bit less than half of the route is considered completed at the moment and there are six
        hiker’s refuges currently open along the route.</string>
    <string name="tab_21"> \u0020 iPhone 11 Pro Max review: The best offering from Apple at the moment
    Apple iPhone 11 Pro Max review:
        \n\n The biggest change in the iPhone 11 Pro series is the triple camera, which adds a new
        ultra-wide angle mode. Here is our review on how it performs.</string>
    <string name="tab_31"> \u0020 Cooking or cookery is the art, technology, science and craft of preparing
        food for consumption. Cooking techniques and ingredients vary widely across the world, from
        grilling food over an open fire to using electric stoves, to baking in various types of ovens,
        reflecting unique environmental, economic, and cultural traditions and trends. Types of cooking
        also depend on the skill levels and training of cooks. Cooking is done both by people in their
        own dwellings and by professional cooks and chefs in restaurants and other food establishments.
        Cooking can also occur through chemical reactions without the presence of heat, such as in ceviche,
        a traditional South American dish where fish is cooked with the acids in lemon or lime juice.\n\n
        Preparing food with heat or fire is an activity unique to humans. It may have started around 2
        million years ago, though archaeological evidence for it reaches no more than 1 million years ago</string>


</resources>
